[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis"], "LOCATION": ["North Miami"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "You know him, you're a neighbor of his, you live near him, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, first of all, you know, I do camps, clinics with kids in the North Miami area and Dennis has helped me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "But what did you know about North Korea and about the regime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenny"], "LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "I mean, did you also know nothing about North Korea, about the regime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Well, I know nothing about Kenny going to North Korea.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Would you have stopped him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I would have stopped him, correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenny"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "I mean, I think, it's important, you know, that that you recognize that Kenny recognized that there was something wrong with Dennis at that point, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Most people will say look, you know, I don't want to be too harsh on you, Kenny because I know that you're the main culprit here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenny", "Dennis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "But I felt, you know, that for all these sporting stars to go out there and embrace this guy who is a pretty evil man running a very evil regime that you, yourself, met him Kim Jong-un, and you shook his hand, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "After the game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Did you know a thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Why am I doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "I knew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "You still shook his hand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "I had no choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Why did you have no choice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Because I was -- I feared, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Did you feel ashamed as you were doing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I felt bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Did you feel that Dennis, in a way, sucked you in the something that you just really should never been there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "First of all, you know, I'm 43 years old, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 150, "question": "It must have made your skin crawl there, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "EX", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "They bought it, you know, after ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 152, "question": "When you're watching it now then what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "All the information ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Look, can I ask you a question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "What does one do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "CD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well, let me ask (inaudible) you came in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "How much did you guys get paid for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "It wasn't about the money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "But, how much was the fee for the plays that went out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Different guys got different fees.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "So, if you were being honest, what did you get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I had a few thousand dollars for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$110,000"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Five, 10?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I got a few thousand dollars for it, $110,000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Why don't you give it all to a kid's charity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I will give a portion to a charity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "And not all of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I will give a portion to a charity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "You don't feel comfortable earning money to go on that trip, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "It wasn't about the money in the first place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Why accept it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Because I got compensated for doing something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Shouldn't you as his agent be recommending or unrecommending that he just basically don't take the money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I'm not in the position to do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Or will give it all to charity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I'm not in the position -- it's his money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Given their statement, do you feel that that is a legitimate stick to go after Chris Christie with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Well, I did during the campaign against him and the fact of the matter is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Well I mean that there's a suggestion today that no actual criminal law may have been broken, do you agree with that or do you think that ultimately there may will be a legal case to launch (ph) in a criminal court?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "EX", "MD", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, this is an abuse of power and an attempt to cover up that abuse of power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What do you think is going to happen with this investigation and indeed the political career of Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well Piers, this is not about polls.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wisniewski", "Barbara Buono"], "LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "He can't run a bridge, how does he want to run a country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "John Wisniewski, Assemblyman from New Jersey, thank you very much and Senator Barbara Buono, thank you very much as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "CD", ",", "CC", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Why wouldn't they do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Because no one wants to go on the record defending something that may ultimately be just proven in a week, or two, or four or six, and that's essentially the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "So, not much, what does he save for his chances of surviving the scandal, and in fact, continuing to become possibly Republican nominee in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well look, what's taken ahead here is the -- Chris Christie that he wanted to presents nationally.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Do you feel there's a double standard here in the way that Democrats are going off to Christie, given the way those three other scandals played out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yeah, well, I knew you couldn't quit me, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "... to the actions of people working for you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "You should, I mean, you should know what's going on and you should also be responsible for the culture that you create in that place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "... to see this as a bit of a side show or not?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And secondly, perhaps winning a generalization if it was against Hillary Clinton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, I know that there's a lot of different stories going back and forth, how he has pulled against Hillary Clinton.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you think that he could still be Republican nominee?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Absolutely, I think that nothing else is going to come up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "So, Ryan, what about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Absolutely, I agree with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger Ailes"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WP$", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Are you surprised by the reaction or was that exactly what you expected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, thanks for having me Piers and you know anyone whose covered Roger Ailes knows that he is the most combative man in the American media.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Why put him on a pedestal of power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "That's a great fascinating question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is that true and if he is so powerful, politically, how come he's effectively they lost the last two elections?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, I think that's a great point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Is that fair assessment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I think that's a fair assessment and that's what my reporting told me after three years in more than 600 interviews.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger Ailes"]}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "How do you plead to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Well Piers, I reached out to Roger Ailes more than a dozen times in person and in writing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "... what did you make about it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "... it's a harrowing story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Final question, is it possible to abhor what Roger Ailes stands for whilst massively admiring his success and ruthless ability to crash rivals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Listen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger Ailes"]}}]